With the release of Cuphead, I realized that I'm terrible at video games.
I've played for 11 hours, and so far I've reached...
This screen. How am I supposed to beat this?
I used to be a respected critic.
Now no one trusts my scores.
My first though was to get better at video games.
No, that requires effort, something I really suck at.
But then...
I came up with a mathematical theorem that should give me the Nobel Prize in math.
Even though it doesn't exist.
Listen students, if getting better in a good game is positive, then getting worse in a bad game must also be a positive.
If I play a bad game bad, I'm good!
I need to find the worst game of all time. Which is famously to be considered to be E.T.
Which is sort of true but E.T. is also the world's first stealth game.
Your goal is to hide from the government. A concept shamelessly ripped-off by the Splinter Cell series. That's a problem.
Years of playing Splinter Cell has made me an E.T. master.
So let's focus on another worstest game of all time.
Superman 64. It's almost as bad as Batman v. Superman.
The goal is to fly through rings. Yep, that's 60% of the game and they fucked that up.
It was actually quite successful, and so broken it drove people into psychiatric wards. I beat in on my first try.
Fine, the third worst worest game is Big Rigs.
Not sure what's bad about it.
Because I don't have a driver's license.
I don't know if this is common when you drive.
If you reverse a car, does it reach light speed?
How did they beat this game?
It doesn't even have an ending.
*Disappointed Sigh*
Good thing all of these games are old. They would never produce something this bad today.
Like Ride to Hell: Oh God Why?
Broken and offensive- everything you do rewards you with weird, clothed humping.
And I beat it!
I understand now. Because I'm bad at good games, I'm the master of terrible games!
I have a solution.
Games aren't always bad because they are broken, terrible, or just worthless.
They can be bad because they ruined an excellent franchise.
Like Sonic '06... uh, excellent.
Here it's not just glitches and bad controls, the entire premise will make you go...
Oh no!
The goal of Sonic '06 is to start an interspecies relationship.
Wait, no, that's something I'm really good at.
Oh no!
What about Link and the Forces of Evil? No, I said bad games not masterpieces.
Another franchise we all loved was Bubsy.
In the 4th game you can't move from side to side.
Some people call it the worst controls of all time, but in reality that's how bobcats move in real life.
People say it's ugly, but so are Picassos.
Another misunderstood masterpiece.
There is one more bad sequel.
There are only two copies. I have one and the other one is in a secret facility, in a secret city, in a secret country.
Worse than all other bad games combined.
It's Halo 4! No, I can't do this.
The menu is so bad it's actually hurting my eyes!
The bad game industry has failed me.
I have no other choice.
I have to make the worst game of all time.
Creating a terrible game requires hard work and passion.
You have to follow ancient traditions.
Tradition 1:
Download Unity.
Ancient Tradition 2:
Apply for Steam Direct.
I know we don't have a game yet, but that shouldn't be a problem.
Huh, it already went through.
I haven't even sent in the application.
Now we're on early access.
The home of the bad game, scientists believe the odds of finding a good game on early access is 1 in 7...
octillion.
That's more than there are atoms on Earth.
Time to create a procedurally generated zombie crafting survival game!
Built with only the freest of 3D models.
It's done!
Wha... What was I supposed to do with it?
I have completely forgotten the original premise of this video.